let questions = [
  {
    section: "Staying Safe Online",
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is a good rule to stay safe from computer viruses?",
    answer: "C) Don't open email attachments if you're not expecting them.",
    options: [
      "A) Download files from the Internet.",
      "B) Open email attachments even if you're not expecting them.",
      "C) Don't open email attachments if you're not expecting them.",
      "D) Share your passwords with friends."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Staying Safe Online",
    numb: 2,
    question: "How can you make sure your antivirus software works well?",
    answer: "C) Keep it up to date by installing the newest version and updating security fixes.",
    options: [
      "A) Never update it and keep using the old version.",
      "B) Run it only when you remember to do so.",
      "C) Keep it up to date by installing the newest version and updating security fixes.",
      "D) Share your antivirus software with your friends."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Staying Safe Online",
    numb: 3,
    question: "Viruses can only be sent by E-mail.",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Staying Safe Online",
    numb: 4,
    question: "Whatever you post online will stay there forever even if you delete it.",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Staying Safe Online",
    numb: 5,
    question: "You can totally share your password with your best friend, you trust them!",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Staying Safe Online",
    numb: 6,
    question: "I have a digital picture of myself, and someone I met online wants to see it. Is it OK to send it to that person?",
    answer: "NO",
    options: [
      "YES",
      "NO"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Staying Safe Online",
    numb: 7,
    question: "Is it a good idea to give your address or phone number to someone you meet online?",
    answer: "NO",
    options: [
      "YES",
      "NO"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Staying Safe Online",
    numb: 8,
    question: "Is it okay to enter a contest on a website from a company or organization you know about that asks for your name and phone number?",
    answer: "NO",
    options: [
      "YES",
      "NO"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Staying Safe Online",
    numb: 9,
    question: "What's a good way to create a strong password for your online accounts?",
    answer: "A) Combine letters, numbers, and symbols, like P@ssw0rd123!",
    options: [
      "A) Combine letters, numbers, and symbols, like P@ssw0rd123!",
      "B) Use your pet's name and birth date.",
      "C) Use a password like 12345.",
      "D) Use the word password as your password."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Staying Safe Online",
    numb: 10,
    question: "How can you keep your computer programs safe?",
    answer: "C) Make copies of them.",
    options: [
      "A) Keep them away from strong magnets.",
      "B) Put them in a safe place.",
      "C) Make copies of them.",
      "D) Keep them in their original boxes."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Cyber Bullying Awareness",
    numb: 11,
    question: "What is cyberbullying?",
    answer: "C) Using the internet to harm or harass others.",
    options: [
      "A) A way to make new friends online.",
      "B) A fun online game.",
      "C) Using the internet to harm or harass others.",
      "D) Sharing positive messages online."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Cyber Bullying Awareness",
    numb: 12,
    question: "How should you respond if someone is mean to you or someone else online?",
    answer: "C) Report it to a trusted adult or a platform's reporting system.",
    options: [
      "A) Be mean back to them.",
      "B) Ignore it and don't tell anyone.",
      "C) Report it to a trusted adult or a platform's reporting system.",
      "D) Encourage others to be mean too."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Cyber Bullying Awareness",
    numb: 13,
    question: "Cybercriminals only target large companies. True or False?",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Cyber Bullying Awareness",
    numb: 14,
    question: "If your friend makes a hurtful video about you online, it's a good idea to make a hurtful video in return.",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Cyber Bullying Awareness",
    numb: 15,
    question: "What should you do if you see a mean comment about someone on a social media post or chat?",
    answer: "C) Stand up for the person being targeted and report the mean commentness helps create a positive and safe online environment.",
    options: [
      "A) Share it with your friends to show how mean people can be.",
      "B) Ignore it and keep scrolling.",
      "C) Stand up for the person being targeted and report the mean commentness helps create a positive and safe online environment.",
      "D) Add your own mean comment to fit in."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Cyber Bullying Awareness",
    numb: 16,
    question: "What should you do if you are being cyber-bullied?",
    answer: "A) All of the above.",
    options: [
      "A) All of the above.",
      "B) Do not respond to the cyberbully.",
      "C) Tell a trusted adult.",
      "D) Block them if you can."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Cyber Bullying Awareness",
    numb: 17,
    question: "Hacking into someone's computer is illegal",
    answer: "YES",
    options: [
      "YES",
      "NO"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Cyber Bullying Awareness",
    numb: 18,
    question: "Anything you say or type online becomes public knowledge and stays online forever...even if you THINK you deleted it.",
    answer: "YES",
    options: [
      "YES",
      "NO"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Cyber Bullying Awareness",
    numb: 19,
    question: "What should you do if you accidentally come across inappropriate or harmful content involving kids online?",
    answer: "B) Report it to the appropriate authorities.",
    options: [
      "A) Share it with friends to raise awareness.",
      "B) Report it to the appropriate authorities.",
      "C) Ignore it and continue browsing.",
      "D) Download and keep it as evidence."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Cyber Bullying Awareness",
    numb: 20,
    question: "If someone is being cyberbullied, what can you do to help them?",
    answer: "D) Stand up for the person being bullied and report the cyberbullying.",
    options: [
      "A) Ignore them and let them handle it themselves.",
      "B) Share the cyberbullying messages with others for fun.",
      "C) Join in and make fun of the person being bullied.",
      "D) Stand up for the person being bullied and report the cyberbullying."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Password Safety",
    numb: 21,
    question: "Below are the tips for good password management except:",
    answer: "A) Use the same password over and over again.",
    options: [
      "A) Use the same password over and over again.",
      "B) Avoid using simple adjacent keyboard combination as your password.",
      "C) Change password often.",
      "D) Make difficult to guess password."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Password Safety",
    numb: 22,
    question: "Which one of the following describes spam?",
    answer: "A) Sending lots of unwanted messages.",
    options: [
      "A) Sending lots of unwanted messages.",
      "B) A delicious type of food.",
      "C) A type of computer game.",
      "D) A friendly email from a family member."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Password Safety",
    numb: 23,
    question: "To use the new social media app that requires users to be 18 years or older, is it okay to lie about your age and sign up yourself.",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Password Safety",
    numb: 24,
    question: "If you receive an email claiming you've won a cash prize and it suggests clicking on the attachment to claim it, you should open the attachment.",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Password Safety",
    numb: 25,
    question: "When creating a password for a new email account, it's a good idea to use a phrase that includes numbers and symbols.",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Password Safety",
    numb: 26,
    question: "The best passwords include your name, age, or birthday.",
    answer: "NO",
    options: [
      "YES",
      "NO"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Password Safety",
    numb: 27,
    question: "Is it a good idea to share your phone or school-related passwords with anyone, even your friends, online or offline?",
    answer: "NO",
    options: [
      "YES",
      "NO"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Password Safety",
    numb: 28,
    question: "Is it safe to use the same password for multiple accounts? ",
    answer: "NO",
    options: [
      "YES",
      "NO"
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Password Safety",
    numb: 29,
    question: "Which of the following is considered unsafe online behavior?",
    answer: "D) Be friend with the people, you don't know.",
    options: [
      "A) Watching YouTube.",
      "B) Typing A Fairy Tale.",
      "C) Playing Games.",
      "D) Be friend with the people, you don't know."
    ]
  },
  {
    section: "Password Safety",
    numb: 30,
    question: "To make a strong password, you need at least how many characters?",
    answer: "B) 8.",
    options: [
      "A) 6.",
      "B) 8.",
      "C) 68.",
      "D) 12."
    ]
  },
  // Add more questions for different sections
];
